SKILLS

Leadership: Design and

Prototyping,

Product Management, User-Centered Design, Lean Product Development, Agile Scrum, 2015 Student Government Vice President for Finance

Technical: Jira, LaTeX, Adobe InDesign & Illustrator, MATLAB, Python, SolidWorks, Arduino, Laser Cutting, ShopBot (CNC router), Manual Mill

SELECTED PROJECTS

SUITable June 2016 - August 2016

Worked on a team of four to create an adaptive jacked for a quadriplegic client. The final product had push-pockets that allow the client to adjust his clothing without help throughout the day and adjustable concealed ventilation flaps for temperature regulation.

ASL Glove October 2015 - December 2015

Worked with three other students to design and fabricate a glove that interprets American Sign Language Fingerspelling and outputs translated text to a phone using flex sensors, an accelerometer, and an Arduino. Published final design and code publicly so that others can replicate our design.

Mobile Planters

Acted as project manager of a nine person, seven week project alongside professional research, design, and fabrication consultants Work-Shop RI. Designed and manufactured a functional, modular plant installation to fit a library with a varied program.

EXPERIENCE

Olin College of Engineering · Principles of Engineering Course Assistant

Needham, MA September 2016 - December 2016

Assisted the teaching team in a project-based course. Responsibilities included providing feedback for student projects and lab assignments, guiding project and team development, holding weekly and by-appointment office hours, answering questions about hardware and software, and grading.

MIT Open Style Lab · Summer Fellow

Cambridge, MA

June 2016 - August 2016

One of twelve fellows selected internationally to work on a team with fashion designers and occupational therapists to create a customized jacket for a quadriplegic client. Focused on usability for the client's physical ability and fabric testing for heat retention and moisture wicking.

Museum of Science · Technical Studio Intern

Boston, MA

June 2016 - August 2016

Engaged students of all ages, especially those underrepresented in STEM, in engineering challenges. Created and facilitated engineering design challenges for museum visitors.

Phone2Action · Product Management Intern

Washington DC

February 2016 - May 2016

Worked with the engineering, customer success, and sales teams to increase communication and streamline the monthly release schedule. Created documentation of new feature requirements, and facilitated feedback about new products. Made user-centric changes to UI and UX of the platform, including creating a style guide. Assisted the engineering team with the design of new features and conducted client trainings.

Olin College of Engineering Library · Summer Intern

Needham, MA

June 2015 - August 2015

Worked on a team of nine students, alumni, faculty, and staff to change the culture and use of the Olin College library. Designed, prototyped, fabricated, and implemented ideas using an agile development strategy.

EDUCATION

Olin College of Engineering

BS, Mechatronics Engineering GPA: 3.57, 2018

Harvard Business School HBX CORe

Course on fundamental business practices. Topics included business analytics, financial accounting, and economics for managers, 2015

Tufts University

Gap Year, School of Engineering, 2014